Guide to the Records of the Grey Art Gallery and Study Center RG 42.5
New York University Archives
- Series I: Exhibition Files, 1961-1988
  - Interrrogating Identity -- English Artists (Donald Rodney), 1990 (Box I:13, Folder 16)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Canadian Art, 1988-Circa 1991 (Box I:13, Folder 17)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Floor Plan, 1991 (Box I:13, Folder 18)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Research, Undated (Box I:13, Folder 19)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Research (2 of 2), 1987-1990 (Box I:13, Folder 20)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Catalogue, Circa 1989-1991 (Box I:13, Folder 21)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Catalogue (Maharaj Essay Draft), 1990-1991 (Box I:13, Folder 22)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Catalogue, 1991 (Box I:13, Folder 23)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Text, Circa 1990-1991 (Box I:13, Folder 24)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Text for II, Circa 1990-1991 (Box I:13, Folder 25)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Programming for II, Circa 1990-1991 (Box I:13, Folder 26)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- July 1990 London Research (1 of 2), 1988-1991 (Box I:13, Folder 27)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- July 1990 London Research (2 of 2), 1988-1991 (Box I:13, Folder 28)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Installation, 1991 (Box I:13, Folder 29)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Checklist, Installation and Packing Instructions, 1990-1993 (Box I:13, Folder 30)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Materials for Venue Book, 1991-1992 (Box I:13, Folder 31)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Press, 1991 March-1993 January (Box I:13, Folder 32)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Duke Press, 1993 January (Box I:13, Folder 33)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Madison Art Center, 1991 March-1992 August (Box I:13, Folder 34)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Madison Press Materials, 1991-1992 (Box I:13, Folder 35)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Miami Press Materials, 1992 June-July (Box I:13, Folder 36)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- MFA Press Materials (Boston), 1991-1992 (Box I:13, Folder 37)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Walker Art Center Press, 1992 (Box I:13, Folder 38)
  - Interrrogating Identity -- Notes and Miscellaneous Items, 1990 July-1991 March (Box I:13, Folder 39)
  - Luis Caballero, 1982-1991 (Box I:13, Folder 40)
  - Hope Sandrow, 1991 (Box I:13, Folder 41)
  - Hope Sandrow -- General Idea, 1991 (Box I:13, Folder 42)
  - General Idea, Circa 1991 (Box I:13, Folder 43)
  - Caballero/Sandrow/General Idea, 1991 May-October (Box I:13, Folder 44)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Checklists, 1990-1991 (Box I:13, Folder 45)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Installation (1 of 2), 1991 (Box I:13, Folder 46)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Installation (2 of 2), 1991 (Box I:13, Folder 47)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Research and Exhibit Material (1 of 3), 1988-1991 (Box I:13, Folder 48)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Research and Exhibit Material (2 of 3), 1990-1991 (Box I:14, Folder 1)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Research and Exhibit Material (3 of 3), 1985-1991 (Box I:14, Folder 2)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Questions, 1988 (Box I:14, Folder 3)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Tour Materials, Circa 1990-1991 (Box I:14, Folder 4)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Public Relations, Circa 1983-1991 (Box I:14, Folder 5)
  - Etruscan Exhibition -- Press, 1991 July-September (Box I:14, Folder 6)
  - Yasuzo Nojima Exhibition -- Plan and Proposal, 1989-1990 (Box I:14, Folder 7)
  - Yasuzo Nojima Exhibit -- Captions, CIrca 1991-1992 (Box I:14, Folder 8)
  - Yasuzo Nojima Exhibit -- Press, 1991 November 26 (Box I:14, Folder 9)
  - Aids Bottle Project, 1991 (Box I:14, Folder 10)
  - Tomie Arai (Window Installation), 1991 September-December (Box I:14, Folder 11)
  - Michael Andrews -- Lists, Labels, Text and Other Miscellaneous, 1986-1991 (Box I:14, Folder 12)
  - Michael Andrews -- Printed Reseach, 1980-1991 (Box I:14, Folder 13)
  - Michael Andrews -- Press, 1992 January-1995 July (Box I:14, Folder 14)
  - Spinster's Tale (Windows) -- Lindsey Walt, 1991 November-1992 June (Box I:14, Folder 15)
  - A Day Without Art -- 1990 (Box I:14, Folder 16)
  - A Day Without Art -- 1991 (Box I:14, Folder 17)
  - A Day Without Art -- 1992 (Box I:14, Folder 18)
  - A Day Without Art -- 1993 (Box I:14, Folder 19)
  - A Day Without Art -- 1994 (Box I:14, Folder 20)
  - A Day Without Art -- Visual Aids Ribbon Project, 1989-1992 (Box I:14, Folder 21)
  - A Day Without Art -- Press, 1989-1993 (Box I:14, Folder 22)
  - A Day Without Art -- Publicity Packet, 1989-1991 (Box I:14, Folder 23)
  - Elaine Reichek: Native Intelligence -- Biography and Slides, Circa 1990-1992 (Box I:14, Folder 24)
  - Elaine Reichek -- Catalogue, Circa 1991-1992 (Box I:14, Folder 25)
  - Elaine Reichek -- Errata Sheets, Undated (Box I:14, Folder 26)
  - Elaine Reichek -- Installation, Circa 1991-1993 (Box I:14, Folder 27)
  - Elaine Reichek -- Lists and Installation, Circa 1991-1992 (Box I:14, Folder 28)
  - Elaine Reichek -- Condition, 1990-1993 (Box I:14, Folder 29)
  - Elaine Reichek -- Press and Photo Material, 1989 February-1993 May (Box I:14, Folder 30)
  - Elaine Reichek -- Drafts, Notes and Other Miscellaneous, Circa 1989-1993 (Box I:14, Folder 31)
  - Elaine Reichek -- Schedule (Cleveland Center for Contemporary Art), 1992 November-1993 April (Box I:14, Folder 32)
  - Elaine Reichek -- Western Washington University, 1992 October-1993 April (Box I:14, Folder 33)
  - Lily van der Stokker (Small Gallery), 1989 October-1992 March (Box I:14, Folder 34)
  - Arne Svenson (Windows), 1989 August-1992 March (Box I:14, Folder 35)
  - Opulent Past -- Artifact Copies (1 of 2), 1992 (Box I:14, Folder 36)
  - Opulent Past -- Artifact Copies (2 of 2), 1992 (Box I:14, Folder 37)
  - Opulent Past -- Catalogue, 1992 (Box I:14, Folder 38)
  - Opulent Past -- Installation, 1992 April-May (Box I:14, Folder 39)
  - Opulent Past -- Invitations, 1992 (Box I:14, Folder 40)
  - Opulent Past -- Press, 1992 June-1993 November (Box I:14, Folder 41)
  - John Kohring (Small Gallery), 1990 October-1992 May (Box I:14, Folder 42)
  - Michael Richards (Windows), 1992 February-December (Box I:14, Folder 43)
  - Camera As Weapon, 1992 (Box I:14, Folder 44)
  - Camera As Weapon -- Press, 1992 September-November (Box I:14, Folder 45)
  - Adrian Piper: Decide Who You Are, 1991 August-1992 July (Box I:14, Folder 46)
  - Adrian Piper -- Magazine, 1993 September-October (Box I:14, Folder 47)
  - Jeff Gates (Windows), 1989 April-1992 August (Box I:14, Folder 48)
  - Australian AIDS Posters, 1992 September-1996 December (Box I:14, Folder 49)
  - Hugh Steers (Small Gallery), 1990-1992 (Box I:14, Folder 50)
  - Gotscho -- Correspondence, 1991 October-1993 January (Box I:15, Folder 1)
  - Gotscho -- Biographies, Circa 1992-1993 (Box I:15, Folder 2)
  - Gotscho -- Exhibit [Installation], Circa 1991-1993 (Box I:15, Folder 3)
  - Gotscho -- Public Relations, 1992 April-1993 March (Box I:15, Folder 4)
  - Joshua Neustein, 1992-1993 (Box I:15, Folder 5)
  - Joshua Neustein -- Press Kit, 1992 August-November (Box I:15, Folder 6)
  - Jane Gifford (Small Gallery), 1992-1993 (Box I:15, Folder 7)
  - Alan Michelson (Windows), 1993 (Box I:15, Folder 8)
  - NetherArt -- Biographies, Undated (Box I:15, Folder 9)
  - NetherArt -- Correspondence, 1992 July-1993 September (Box I:15, Folder 10)
  - NetherArt -- Exhibition, 1992-1993 (Box I:15, Folder 11)
  - NetherArt -- Public Relations, 1993 March-July (Box I:15, Folder 12)
  - NetherArt -- Registration, 1990 November-1993 August (Box I:15, Folder 13)
  - Other Borders -- Biographies, 1991-1993 (Box I:15, Folder 14)
  - Other Borders -- Correspondence, 1992 September-1993 May (Box I:15, Folder 15)
  - Other Borders -- Exhibition, 1993 (Box I:15, Folder 16)
  - Other Borders -- Public Relations, 1991 May-1993 May (Box I:15, Folder 17)
  - Other Borders -- Registration, 1993 February-1994 March (Box I:15, Folder 18)
  - The Museum in the Gallery -- Exhibition, Circa 1993 (Box I:15, Folder 19)
  - The Museum in the Gallery -- Public Relations, 1993 May-July (Box I:15, Folder 20)
  - Matthew Benedict (Windows), 1993 March-May (Box I:15, Folder 21)
  - George Platt Lynes -- Biographies, 1992 October-November (Box I:15, Folder 22)
  - George Platt Lynes -- Correspondence (1 of 2), 1992 February-1994 October (Box I:15, Folder 23)
  - George Platt Lynes -- Correspondence (2 of 2), 1990-1994 (Box I:15, Folder 24)
  - George Platt Lynes -- Exhibition, 1993 (Box I:15, Folder 25)
  - George Platt Lynes -- Public Relations, 1993-1994 (Box I:15, Folder 26)
  - George Platt Lynes -- Registration, 1993 July-1994 November (Box I:15, Folder 27)
  - Bill Jacobson (Small Gallery), 1993 (Box I:15, File 28)
  - Jim Hodges (Windows), 1993-1995 (Box I:15, Folder 29)
  - Anyone in New York -- Biography, 1993 October (Box I:15, Folder 30)
  - Anyone in New York -- Correspondence, 1993 May-December (Box I:15, Folder 31)
  - Anyone in New York -- Exhibition, Circa 1992-1993 (Box I:15, Folder 32)
  - Anyone in New York -- Public Relations, 1993 June-December (Box I:15, Folder 33)
  - Brief Encounters (Small Gallery) -- Registration, 1993 October-1994 January (Box I:15, Folder 34)
  - Simon Patterson (Small Gallery), 1993 August-1994 April (Box I:15, Folder 35)
  - Lydia Schouten (Windows), 1993 January-November (Box I:15, Folder 36)
  - Art About Aids -- Biographies, 1989-Circa 1994 (Box I:15, Folder 37)
  - Art About Aids -- Correspondence, 1989 February-1993 December (Box I:15, Folder 38)
  - Art About Aids -- Exhibition, Circa 1993-1994 (Box I:15, Folder 39)
  - Art About Aids -- Public Relations (1 of 3), 1992 January-1994 July (Box I:15, Folder 40)
  - Art About Aids -- Public Relations (2 of 3), 1991 August-1994 February (Box I:16, Folder 1)
  - Art About Aids -- Public Relations (3 of 3), 1993 February-1994 April (Box I:16, Folder 2)
  - Art About Aids -- Registration, 1991 March-1994 April (Box I:16, Folder 3)
  - Visual Aids (Small Gallery), Circa 1993-1994 (Box I:16, Folder 4)
  - Joseph Stashkevetch (Windows), CIrca 1993-1994 (Box I:16, Folder 5)
  - Todd Watts -- Biographies, 1994 (Box I:16, Folder 6)
  - Todd Watts -- Correspondence, 1990 February-1994 June (Box I:16, Folder 7)
  - Todd Watts -- Exhibition, Circa 1993-1994 (Box I:16, Folder 8)
  - Todd Watts -- Public Relations, 1979-1994 November (Box I:16, Folder 9)
  - Todd Watts -- Registration, 1993 December-1994 May (Box I:16, Folder 10)
  - Three Women in Black (Windows), 1994 (Box I:16, Folder 11)
  - 1969: A Year Revisited -- Correspondence, 1994 April-June (Box I:16, Folder 12)
  - 1969: A Year Revisited -- Exhibition, Circa 1992-1994 (Box I:16, Folder 13)
  - 1969: A Year Revisited -- Public Relations, 1969 January-1994 July (Box I:16, Folder 14)
  - 1969: A Year Revisited -- Registration, 1994 February-August (Box I:16, Folder 15)
  - Rob Wynne (Windows), 1993 October-1994 July (Box I:16, Folder 16)
  - Arne Svenson (Small Gallery), 1994 (Box I:16, Folder 17)
  - Willie Doherty -- Biographies, 1992 November (Box I:16, Folder 18)
  - Willie Doherty -- Correspondence, 1992 March-1994 August (Box I:16, Folder 19)
  - Willie Doherty -- Public Relations, 1990 October-1994 October (Box I:16, Folder 20)
  - Willie Doherty -- Registration, 1994 March-December (Box I:16, Folder 21)
  - John Defazio (Small Gallery), 1993-1994 (Box I:16, Folder 22)
  - Rene Santos -- Biographies, 1994 September (Box I:16, Folder 23)
  - Rene Santos -- Correspondence, 1982-1995 July (Box I:16, Folder 24)
  - Rene Santos -- Exhibition, Circa 1992-1994 (Box I:16, Folder 25)
  - Rene Santos -- Public Relations, 1994-1995 (Box I:16, Folder 26)
  - Rene Santos -- Registration (Miscellaneous Correspondence, Checklists, 1 of 2), Circa 1994-1995 (Box I:16, Folder 27)
  - Rene Santos -- Registration (Miscellaneous Correspondence, Checklists, 2 of 2), 1994 August-October (Box I:16, Folder 28)
  - Rene Santos -- Registration (Packing List, Condition), 1994 September-December (Box I:16, Folder 29)
  - Narelle Jubelin -- Biographies, 1992-1994 (Box I:16, Folder 30)
  - Narelle Jubelin -- Correspondence, 1993 May-1995 February (Box I:16, Folder 31)
  - Narelle Jubelin -- Exhibition, 1994-Circa 1995 (Box I:16, Folder 32)
  - Narelle Jubelin -- Public Relations, 1994 January-1995 February (Box I:16, Folder 33)
  - Narelle Jubelin -- Registration, 1994 July-1995 April (Box I:16, Folder 34)
  - Jason Reed (Small Gallery and Windows), 1994 December-1995 February (Box I:16, Folder 35)
  - Ann Mandelbaum -- Biographies, Undated (Box I:16, Folder 36)
  - Ann Mandelbaum -- Correspondence, 1994 January-October (Box I:16, Folder 37)
  - Ann Mandelbaum -- Exhibition, Circa 1994-1995 (Box I:16, Folder 38)
  - Ann Mandelbaum -- Public Relations, 1994-1995 (Box I:16, Folder 39)
  - Ann Mandelbaum -- Registration, 1995 March (Box I:16, Folder 40)
  - John Lindell (Small Gallery) -- Exhibition, 1995 March (Box I:16, Folder 41)
  - John Lindell (Small Gallery) -- Public Relations, 1995 April-May (Box I:16, Folder 42)
  - John Lindell (Small Gallery) -- Registration, 1995 March (Box I:16, Folder 43)
  - Ed McGowan (Windows), 1995 (Box I:16, Folder 44)
  - The Creative Will (Multiple Sclerosis), 1992-1995 (Box I:16, Folder 45)
  - The Creative Will (Multiple Sclerosis) -- Project Rembrandt, 1995 (Box I:16, Folder 46)
  - The Creative Will (Multiple Sclerosis) -- Biographies, 1981-1995 (Box I:17, Folder 1)
  - The Creative Will (Multiple Sclerosis) -- Entry Forms, Circa 1993-1995 (Box I:17, Folder 2)
  - The Creative Will (Multiple Sclerosis) -- Registration, 1995 (Box I:17, Folder 3)
  - Mark Beard (Windows), 1995-1996 (Box I:17, Folder 4)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Background Articles, Reviews, etc., 1992 March-Circa 1996 (Box I:17, Folder 5)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Catalogue Miscellaneous (1 of 2), 1996 (Box I:17, Folder 6)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Catalogue Miscellaneous (2 of 2), Circa 1995-1997 (Box I:17, Folder 7)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Correspondence, 1995 September-1997 August (Box I:17, Folder 8)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Development, 1995-1996 (Box I:17, Folder 9)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Exhibition Design, Circa 1994-1997 (Box I:17, Folder 10)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Exhibition List, 1995-1996 (Box I:17, Folder 11)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Installation, 1996-1997 (Box I:17, Folder 12)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Miscellaneous (1 of 2), 1994-1996 (Box I:17, Folder 13)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Miscellaneous (2 of 2), 1996 (Box I:17, Folder 14)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Press, 1996-1997 (Box I:17, Folder 15)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Registration, 1995 May-1997 January (Box I:17, Folder 16)
  - Traditions/Tensions -- Resumes, Undated (Box I:17, Folder 17)
  - Artists from Japan -- Philip Morris Art Award, 1995 August-1996 April (Box I:17, Folder 18)
  - Artists from Japan -- Philip Morris Art Award Selection (1 of 3), 1996 February-July (Box I:17, Folder 19)
  - Artists from Japan -- Philip Morris Art Award Selection (2 of 3), Circa 1996 (Box I:17, Folder 20)
  - Artists from Japan -- Philip Morris Art Award Selection (3 of 3), 1996 (Box I:17, Folder 21)
  - Artists from Japan -- Artists Shown, 1996 (Box I:17, Folder 22)
  - Artists from Japan -- Condition Reports, 1996-1997 (Box I:17, Folder 23)
  - Artists from Japan -- Exhibition Signage, 1996 (Box I:17, Folder 24)
  - Artists from Japan -- Postponement, 1996 (Box I:17, Folder 25)
  - Artists from Japan -- Review, 1997 February 1 (Box I:17, Folder 26)
  - Artists from Japan -- Shipment and Installation, 1996 June-1997 February (Box I:17, Folder 27)
  - Artists from Japan -- Shipment and Installation (Documents), 1996-1997 (Box I:17, Folder 28)
- Series II: Administrative Files, 1961-1988
  - Subseries A: Correspondence, 1959-1977
    - Chronological Miscellaneous Coorespondence, 1959-1969 (Box II:1, Folder 1)
    - Chronological Faculty Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box II:1, Folder 2)
    - Chronological File -- February-July 1967, 1967 February-July (Box II:1, Folder 3)
    - Chronological File -- August-December 1967, 1967 August-December (Box II:1, Folder 4)
    - Chronological File -- January-June 1968, 1968 January-June (Box II:1, Folder 5)
    - Chronological File -- July-December 1968, 1968 July-December (Box II:1, Folder 6)
    - Chronological File -- 1969 (Box II:1, Folder 7)
    - Chronological File -- 1970 (Box II:1, Folder 8)
    - Chronological File -- 1971 (Box II:1, Folder 9)
    - Chronological File -- 1972 (Box II:1, Folder 10)
    - Chronological File -- 1973 (1 of 2) (Box II:1, Folder 11)
    - Chronological File -- 1973 (2 of 2) (Box II:1, Folder 12)
    - Chronological File -- 1974 (Box II:1, Folder 13)
    - Chronological File -- 1975 (1 of 2) (Box II:1, Folder 14)
    - Chronological File -- 1975 (2 of 2) (Box II:1, Folder 15)
    - Chronological File - JAS (1 of 2), 1976 (Box II:1, Folder 16)
    - Chronological File - JAS (2 of 2), 1976 (Box II:1, Folder 17)
    - Chronological File - JAS, 1976-1977 (Box II:1, Folder 18)
    - Thank You Letters -- 1967-1969 (Box II:1, Folder 19)
    - Thank You Letters -- 1969-1971 (Box II:1, Folder 20)
  - Subseries B: Grey, 1973-1980
    - Donor, 1973-1975 (Box II:1, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1980 May (Box II:1, Folder 22)
    - Honorary Dinner, 1979-1980 (Box II:1, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence for Mrs. Abby, 1975-1979 (Box II:1, Folder 24)
  - Subseries C: WNYC, 1968-1973
    - Radio - "View on Art", 1972-1973 (Box II:1, Folder 25)
    - Radio - "View on Art", 1972-1973 (Box II:1, Folder 26)
    - TV - One to One (1 of 2), 1968-1972 (Box II:1, Folder 27)
    - TV - One to One (2 of 2), 1968-1972 (Box II:1, Folder 28)
    - TV, 1969-1970 (Box II:1, Folder 29)
    - TV, 1970-1971 (Box II:1, Folder 30)
    - TV, 1971-1972 (Box II:1, Folder 31)
    - TV (1 of 2), 1972-1973 (Box II:1, Folder 32)
    - TV (2 of 2), 1972-1973 (Box II:1, Folder 33)
  - Subseries D: Development, 1964-198
    - AFA Ancient Mexico Exhibit, 1964 November 3 (Box II:2, Folder 1)
    - Loan Return Forms -- New York Painter, 1967 (Box II:2, Folder 2)
    - Lenders, 1967 April-October (Box II:2, Folder 3)
    - New York State Council on the Arts - Grant Application, 1970 June-August (Box II:2, Folder 4)
    - 1971 Grant Application -- NYSCA (Box II:2, Folder 5)
    - Exhibitions: University of Connecticut, 1972 October 2 (Box II:2, Folder 6)
    - Sunrise Semester, 1972 (Box II:2, Folder 7)
    - Helena Rubenstein Foundation Grant, 1973-1974 (Box II:2, Folder 8)
    - New York State Council on the Arts, 1973-1975 (Box II:2, Folder 9)
    - Exhibitions Print Show - Hudson River Museum, 1973 January 13-March 4 (Box II:2, Folder 10)
    - Alan Sonfist - Rejected Exhibition Proposal, 1973 December-1975 December (Box II:2, Folder 11)
    - Grant Proposals, 1974 (Box II:2, Folder 12)
    - NEH Grants Rejected -- Ashcan Painters, 1974 (Box II:2, Folder 13)
    - Draft Proposal -- NYSCA General Operations, 1974-1975 (Box II:2, Folder 14)
    - NEA Grant -- Prints and Techniques, 1975-1976 (Box II:2, Folder 15)
    - Prints and Technique Working File, 1976 March-April (Box II:2, Folder 16)
    - NYSCA 2nd Proposal - Joy Gordon, 1975-1976 (Box II:2, Folder 17)
    - Loans -- Sara Roby Exhibition, 1976 January-March (Box II:2, Folder 18)
    - Udine Receipts, 1976 July-August (Box II:2, Folder 19)
    - NYSCA Program Proposal (1 of 2), 1976-1977 (Box II:2, Folder 20)
    - NYSCA Program Proposal (2 of 2), 1976-1977 (Box II:2, Folder 21)
    - Circa 1776 NEA Grant, 1976-1977 (Box II:2, Folder 22)
    - Circa 1776 Loans, 1976 June-October (Box II:2, Folder 23)
    - 1776 Exhibition Loans, 1976 June-November (Box II:2, Folder 24)
    - NYSCA Grant Preparatory Notes, circa 1976-1978 (Box II:2, Folder 25)
    - Cooper-Hewitt Museum Show, 1976 June-December (Box II:2, Folder 26)
    - Tanavolil Shipping and Insurance, 1976 August-1977 January (Box II:2, Folder 27)
    - Parviz Tanavoli Exhibition Billing, 1976 November 10-23 (Box II:2, Folder 28)
    - Beatrix Potter -- American Lenders Correspondence (1 of 2), 1976 November-1977 July (Box II:2, Folder 29)
    - Beatrix Potter -- American Lenders Correspondence (2 of 2), 1976 November-1977 July (Box II:2, Folder 30)
    - Beatrix Potter Correspondence to Armitt Trust, 1976 November-1978 January (Box II:2, Folder 31)
    - National Trust -- Beatrix Potter Exhibit (1 of 3), 1976 December-1984 November (Box II:2, Folder 32)
    - National Trust -- Beatrix Potter Exhibit (2 of 3), 1976 December-1984 November (Box II:2, Folder 33)
    - National Trust -- Beatrix Potter Exhibit (3 of 3), 1976 December-1984 November (Box II:2, Folder 34)
    - Information on Lenders [Beatrix Potter] (1 of 2), 1977 February-May (Box II:2, Folder 35)
    - Information on Lenders [Beatrix Potter] (2 of 2), 1977 February-May (Box II:2, Folder 36)
    - Beatrix Potter Toronto-Boston Loans, 1977 April-June (Box II:2, Folder 37)
    - Grants Pending/Accepted -- NEH Futurist Exhibition (1 of 2), 1977 (Box II:2, Folder 38)
    - Grants Pending/Accepted -- NEH Futurist Exhibition (2 of 2), 1977 (Box II:2, Folder 39)
    - Ree Morton Loans, 1977 May-August (Box II:2, Folder 40)
    - Drawing and Collage Loans, 1977 May-October (Box II:2, Folder 41)
    - Philadelphia Museum Correspondence - Gallery of Living Art Revisited, 1977-1978 (Box II:2, Folder 42)
    - Berkshire Museum Correspondence - "Gallery of Living Art", 1977-1978 (Box II:2, Folder 43)
    - Panoramic Photography, 1977-1979 (Box II:2, Folder 44)
    - Panoramic Photography Lenders A-K, 1977 May-1978 January (Box II:2, Folder 45)
    - History of Panoramic Photo - Insurance, 1977 May-September (Box II:2, Folder 46)
    - Panoramic Photography Lenders L, 1977 June-December (Box II:2, Folder 47)
    - Panoramic Photography Lenders M-Z (1 of 2), 1977 June-December (Box II:3, Folder 1)
    - Panoramic Photography Lenders M-Z (2 of 2), 1977 June-December (Box II:3, Folder 2)
    - Avedisian/Hennessy/Grosman Loan Forms and Memos, 1977 January-1978 December 29 (Box II:3, Folder 3)
    - Wilmarth/Sandman Exhibition (Insurance and Transportation), 1977 November-1978 July (Box II:3, Folder 4)
    - Wilmarth Black/White Photos, 1978 September-October (Box II:3, Folder 5)
    - The Jewish Way of Death - NEH (Pending) (Rejected), 1978 (Box II:3, Folder 6)
    - Frank Lloyd Wright -- Works in NY Show Only (1 of 2), 1978 May-December (Box II:3, Folder 7)
    - Frank Lloyd Wright -- Works in NY Show Only (2 of 2), 1978 May-December (Box II:3, Folder 8)
    - Frank Lloyd Wright -- Registrar's Files Miscellaneous, 1978 September-1979 January (Box II:3, Folder 9)
    - Gallatin -- Lenders, 1978-1979 (Box II:3, Folder 10)
    - On the Square -- NEH Planning, 1978-1979 (Box II:3, Folder 11)
    - Tiffany -- Lenders A-L (1 of 2), 1978 March-1979 June (Box II:3, Folder 12)
    - Tiffany -- Lenders A-L (2 of 2), 1978 March-1979 December (Box II:3, Folder 13)
    - Tiffany -- Lenders M-Z (1 of 2), 1978 March-1979 June (Box II:3, Folder 14)
    - Tiffany -- Lenders M-Z (2 of 2), 1978 March-1979 June (Box II:3, Folder 15)
    - Tiffany -- Auxiliary Loans, 1979 March-May (Box II:3, Folder 16)
    - Russian Show -- NEH (Revised), 1979 (Box II:3, Folder 17)
    - Looking at Art -- NEA Grant, 1979 (Box II:3, Folder 18)
    - Life -- Blank Contracts, 1979 November 5 (Box II:13, Folder 18)
    - Life -- Blank Facilities Reports, Undated (Box II:13, Folder 19)
    - Life -- Bookings (No Response or Rejections), 1977 November-1979 October (Box II:13, Folder 20)
    - Life -- Bookings Pending, 1979 May-1980 December (Box II:13, Folder 21)
    - Life -- Budget, 1979 May-August (Box II:13, Folder 22)
    - Life -- Catalog Orders, 1979 June-September (Box II:13, Folder 23)
    - Life -- Time, Inc. Correspondence, 1978 August-1979 April (Box II:13, Folder 24)
    - Life -- Correspondence, 1979 May-August (Box II:13, Folder 25)
    - Life -- Crate List, Circa 1979-1980 (Box II:13, Folder 26)
    - Life -- Frames and Crates (Costs), 1979 March (Box II:13, Folder 27)